http://www.brunotti.com/en/privacy.html

Shoppingcart - 0 products
Discount:
Payment costs:
Delivery:
Total:
Check out
Continue shopping
CHOOSE YOUR SIZE...
PLACE IN SHOPPING CART
SOLD OUT - UPDATE ME WHEN IN STOCK
Brunottishop Privacy Notice
Company Address:
Brunotti e-shop.com B.V.
V.A.T. number: NL-8215.15.263B01
During all visits on our website our web server will recognize automatically your IP address. We save the following information after each visit on our website:
Your e-mail address when you have placed an order or sent a question on our website
Your e-mail address after you have communicated this with us
All information concerning the pages you have visited
All information you have given us voluntarily
The information will be used for internal use and will not be shared with third parties for commercial use.
On this website we use cookies. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide us with information concerning your visit on our website and how you got there.
After subscribing to our newsletter you can always unsubscribe by clicking on the "Unsubscribe" link on every
news letter e-mail. We greatly respect your e-mail privacy. All e-mail addresses entered into our news letter subscription list will not be shared with third parties, but will merely be used for the Brunottishop news letter.
We do not have partnerships or special relationships with third parties.
For all confidential information, such as financial or health information we use a secured server. You will be informed of the use of this server by a pop-up window on our website. We have implemented all security measures that are needed to avoid loss or illegitimate use of the information, we receive on our website.
How can you contact us?
If you wish to react to our privacy policy, you can contact us
by e-mail: info@brunottishop.com
by postal mail: Brunotti e-shop.com B.V. Gezellenstraat 18, 3861 RD Nijkerk, Netherlands
Communication by e-mail:
If you no longer wish to receive our e-mails, please use the above mentioned e-mail address to unsubscribe.
Communication by postal mail:
If you have provided us with your postal address you will only receive the information you have asked for on that address.
Communication by phone:
If you have provided us with your phone number on our website, you will only be contacted by phone in order to inform you about your online order.
Our company can use the customer information for new purposes that are not yet part of our privacy notice. In that case we will contact you first before using your information for those new purposes. This way we can inform you properly in advance of any changes of our privacy notice and protect your personal information, giving you the opportunity to refuse your participation in this.
By request we provide the visitors of our website with all their information we keep. If you wish to access this information, please contact us by using the above mentioned (e-mail) address.
By request we give the visitors of our website the opportunity to change or correct their personal information. If you wish to do so, please contact us by using the above mentioned (e-mail) address.
If you think that our website does not correspond with our privacy notice, please contact us by using the above mentioned (e-mail) address.
